Preliminary Guide to the Robert Edward Dawson Papers, 1939-1998
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession 2001-0153 (Box 12)
  - Contents of box 17:, Subject Files: D, N, P (Box 17)
  - Contents of box 18:, Subject Files: R-Z (Box 18)
  - NC health services (Box 18)
  - Magazines and journals (Box 18)
  - Contents of box 19:, Statements from Mechanics and Farmers Bank (Box 19)
  - Receipts (Box 19)
  - Contents of box 20:, Bank statements (Box 20)
  - Journals, Magazines, and Directories (Box 20)
  - Contents of legal size box 21: (Box 21)
    - Magazines, Fliers, and Journals (Box 21)
    - Mutual Savings and Loans, [from box 7] (Box 21)
    - Paine Webber, [from box 17] (Box 21)